Donald and Charlotte MacJannet Papers MS024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Personal papers, 1824 -- 1999; 1916 -- 1986; MS024.001; 27.9 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 2 Digital Object(s)
  - Personal letters, 1946; MS024.001.138.00049 (Box 138)
  - Personal letters, 1946; MS024.001.138.00050 (Box 138)
  - Personal letters, Charlotte B. MacJannet, 1935 -- 1970; MS024.001.138.00051 (Box 138)
    Mostly letters from Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet to Donald MacJannet. Some date from the time of their marriage.
  - Personal letters, Charlotte B. MacJannet, 1935 -- 1970; MS024.001.138.00052 (Box 138)
  - Personal letters, Charlotte B. MacJannet, 1935 -- 1970; MS024.001.138.00053 (Box 138)
  - Personal letters from campers and counselors, 1950; MS024.001.138.00054 (Box 138)
  - World Youth Forum, 1976; MS024.001.138.00055 (Box 138)
    Material from the MacJannet's involvement with the organization.
  - Arlington material, 1945; MS024.001.139.00001 (Box 139)
    Letters from the MacJannets stay in Arlington, MA during World War II.
  - 'Biography', 1915 -- 1980; MS024.001.139.00002 (Box 139)
    From folder marked biography, contains items relating the events of Donald MacJannet's life including service during WWI, education, teaching, and awards.
  - 'Biography', 1915 -- 1980; MS024.001.139.00003 (Box 139)
    From folder marked biography, contains items realting the events of Donald MacJannet's life including service during WWI, education, teaching, and awards.
  - 'Biography' Tufts Class Day book, 1913; MS024.001.139.00004 (Box 139)
  - Christmas letters from MacJannets, 1990; MS024.001.139.00005 (Box 139)
  - Correspondence with Andre Schmitt, 1955; MS024.001.139.00006 (Box 139)
    Andre Schmitt, from Paris, hoped to visit American camps in the summer of 1955 which Donald MacJannet was helping him with. The trip fell through.
  - Documents, 1948; MS024.001.139.00007 (Box 139)
    Includes material on attempt to recover losses of WWII from the St. Cloud school, as well as official French documents relating to camp.
  - 'Donald - his thoughts in writing and other unsorted items', 1924; MS024.001.139.00008 (Box 139)
    Items collected and written by Donald MacJannet.
  - Family, 1980 -- 1982; MS024.001.139.00009 (Box 139)
    Mostly letters.
  - Family, 1980 -- 1982; MS024.001.139.00010 (Box 139)
  - Family, 1980 -- 1982; MS024.001.139.00011 (Box 139)
  - Fiftieth reunion at Tufts, 1966; MS024.001.139.00012 (Box 139)
    50th reunion of the class of 1916.
  - 'Jean-Patten-Lottie' letters, 1960 -- 1970; MS024.001.139.00013 (Box 139)
  - 'Jean-Patten-Lottie' letters, 1960 -- 1970; MS024.001.139.00014 (Box 139)
  - Letters, 1920 -- 1955; MS024.001.139.00015 (Box 139)
  - Letters, 1945; MS024.001.139.00016 (Box 139)
    Includes material on shipping and supplies.
  - Letters, 1945; MS024.001.139.00017 (Box 139)
  - Letters to Charlotte B. MacJannet, 1991; MS024.001.139.00018 (Box 139)
  - Letters to Mr. Mac, 1947 -- 1949; MS024.001.139.00019 (Box 139)
    Includes letters from Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet.
  - Letters to Mr. Mac, 1947 -- 1949; MS024.001.139.00020 (Box 139)
  - Letters to Mr. Mac, 1947 -- 1949; MS024.001.139.00021 (Box 139)
  - Muller-Blensdorf correspondence, 1935; MS024.001.139.00022 (Box 139)
    Correspondence between Donald and Charlotte MacJannet and her family, particularly with her sister Ilse and brother-in-law Ernst Muller-Blensdorf.
  - Muller-Blensdorf correspondence, 1935; MS024.001.139.00023 (Box 139)
  - Muller-Blensdorf correspondence, 1935; MS024.001.139.00024 (Box 139)
  - Muller-Blensdorf correspondence, 1935; MS024.001.139.00025 (Box 139)
  - Personal, 1969 -- 1971; MS024.001.139.00026 (Box 139)
    Mostly letters but also includes other documents.
  - Personal letters, 1946; MS024.001.139.00027 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1946; MS024.001.139.00028 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1949 -- 1952; MS024.001.139.00029 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1949 -- 1952; MS024.001.139.00030 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1949 -- 1952; MS024.001.139.00031 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1949 -- 1952; MS024.001.139.00032 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1949 -- 1952; MS024.001.139.00033 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1949 -- 1952; MS024.001.139.00034 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1949 -- 1952; MS024.001.139.00035 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters, 1949 -- 1952; MS024.001.139.00036 (Box 139)
  - Personal letters and material, Charlotte B. MacJannet, 1990; MS024.001.139.00037 (Box 139)
  - Personal material, 1920; MS024.001.139.00038 (Box 139)
    Includes letters from the American Embassy in Paris.
  - Personal material, 1920 -- 1985; MS024.001.139.00039 (Box 139)
    Includes a 1940 temporary circulation permit from the French government.
  - 'Petra und Bernd', 1983; MS024.001.139.00040 (Box 139)
  - Round Robin Letters, 1960 -- 1970; MS024.001.139.00041 (Box 139)
  - Round Robin Letters, 1960 -- 1970; MS024.001.139.00042 (Box 139)
  - Trip to Japan - letters, diary, 1959; MS024.001.139.00043 (Box 139)
    Material belonging to Jean MacJannet Foster.
  - Trip to Japan - letters, diary, 1959; MS024.001.139.00044 (Box 139)
  - Trip to Japan - diary, 1959; MS024.001.139.00045 (Box 139)
  - American relief for France, 1946; MS024.001.140.00001 (Box 140)
    Includes commentary on the France Rebuilds film by Donald MacJannet.
  - Arlington/Rose Tuller, 1955; MS024.001.140.00002 (Box 140)
    Correspondence relating to the sale of the MacJannet's house and furniture in Arlington.
  - Arlington/Rose Tuller, 1955; MS024.001.140.00003 (Box 140)
  - 'Australie', 1970; MS024.001.140.00004 (Box 140)
    Letters, mostly from Australia, to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet. Includes Dalcroze and Rythmique material.
  - 'Australie', 1970; MS024.001.140.00005 (Box 140)
  - 'Church', 1980; MS024.001.140.00006 (Box 140)
    Letters pertaining to the Emmanuel church in Geneva and PECUSA.
  - Correspondence after camp, 1952; MS024.001.140.00007 (Box 140)
  - 'Correspondence with family', 1945; MS024.001.140.00008 (Box 140)
    Mostly correspondence with Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's family in Germany, some letters sent through Trudi Biedermann. Also included is some medical correspondence.
  - 'Correspondence with family', 1945; MS024.001.140.00009 (Box 140)
  - 'Correspondence with family', 1945; MS024.001.140.00010 (Box 140)
  - 'Correspondence with Ilse and Ernst', 1938; MS024.001.140.00011 (Box 140)
    Letters from Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's sister and brother-in-law and their children Eva, Gonda and Klaus. Some from Norway.
  - 'Correspondence with Ilse and Ernst', 1938; MS024.001.140.00012 (Box 140)
  - 'Early Souvenirs', 1910 -- 1940; MS024.001.140.00013 (Box 140)
    Mostly letters to Donald MacJannet 1914-1915.
  - 'Early Souvenirs', 1910 -- 1940; MS024.001.140.00014 (Box 140)
  - 'Early Souvenirs', 1910 -- 1940; MS024.001.140.00015 (Box 140)
  - 'Early Souvenirs', 1910 -- 1940; MS024.001.140.00016 (Box 140)
  - 'Father's letters', 1933 -- 1946; MS024.001.140.00017 (Box 140)
    Letters from Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's father Otto Blensdorf.
  - Lathwesen, 1948; MS024.001.140.00018 (Box 140)
    Letters from the Blensdorf family.
  - Letters, 1940 -- 1945; MS024.001.140.00019 (Box 140)
    Letters from and concerning Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's family during war, also letters 'from friends in England.'
  - Letters, 1950 -- 1970; MS024.001.140.00020 (Box 140)
    Letters mostly addressed to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet. Photographs removed and placed in MS024/007.
  - Letters, 1950 -- 1970; MS024.001.140.00021 (Box 140)
  - Letters from family to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1949; MS024.001.140.00022 (Box 140)
    Includes letters from Ilse Blensdorf.
  - Letters from family to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1949; MS024.001.140.00023 (Box 140)
  - Letters from Ilse, 1950; MS024.001.140.00024 (Box 140)
    Also includes letters from Ilse Blensdorf's three children, Eva, Gonda and Klaus.
  - Letters from Ilse, 1950; MS024.001.140.00025 (Box 140)
  - Letters, 1955; MS024.001.140.00026 (Box 140)
    From folder labeled 'Hans + Inge briefe.' Family letters to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet.
  - Letters, 1955; MS024.001.140.00027 (Box 140)
  - Letters, 1955; MS024.001.140.00028 (Box 140)
  - Letters, to Charlotte B. MacJannet, 1960; MS024.001.140.00029 (Box 140)
    Letters in German, English, French and Swedish. Includes letters from family members including sister Ilse and niece Ilo.
  - 'Mrs. MacJannet, die kinder', 1938 -- 1988; MS024.001.140.00030 (Box 140)
    Letters from Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's sister Ilse. Also included is material on Ilse's three children and their education.
  - 'Mrs. MacJannet, die kinder', 1938 -- 1988; MS024.001.140.00031 (Box 140)
  - Personal letters, 1919 -- 1980; MS024.001.140.00032 (Box 140)
    Bulk of material from 1980s.
  - Personal letters, 1955; MS024.001.140.00033 (Box 140)
    From loose pile. Most of the correspondence relates to the sale of the MacJannet's home in Arlington, MA. Photos removed and put in MS024/007.
  - Personal material, 1985; MS024.001.140.00034 (Box 140)
    Mostly letters to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet. Some material relating to her interest in the Piper's Guild.
  - Personal material, 1985; MS024.001.140.00035 (Box 140)
  - Priory, 4th centenial of St Francois de Sales, 1967; MS024.001.140.00036 (Box 140)
    Material relating to 4th centenial celebration in Talloires. Also contains some Entretiens material.
  - Priory, 4th centenial of St Francois de Sales, 1967; MS024.001.140.00037 (Box 140)
  - Reports on Germany, 1945; MS024.001.140.00038 (Box 140)
    Letters and newsletters about the state of post-World War II Germany.
  - 'Showing of camp movies in England and Italy', 1932 -- 1933; MS024.001.140.00039 (Box 140)
    Also includes some camp material from 1946 such as food ration stamps.
  - 'Showing of camp movies in England and Italy', 1932 -- 1933; MS024.001.140.00040 (Box 140)
  - 'Sturtz', 1945; MS024.001.140.00041 (Box 140)
    All material in German. Much of it from WWII period, some letters ending with 'Heil Hitler'. Includes lists of furniture.
  - Letters to Jean, 1958 -- 1959; MS024.001.141.00001 (Box 141)
    Mostly letters from Donald MacJannet to his sister, Jean MacJannet Foster.
  - Agnes Kleberg, 1959; MS024.001.141.00002 (Box 141)
    Letters to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, mostly in Swedish.
  - 'Boursiers' (Scholarships), 1946; MS024.001.141.00003 (Box 141)
    Letters and material concerning French young adults sent as counselors to American camps in the summer of 1946.
  - 'Boursiers' (Scholarships), 1946; MS024.001.141.00004 (Box 141)
  - 'Boursiers' (Scholarships), 1946; MS024.001.141.00005 (Box 141)
  - 'Boursiers' (Scholarships), 1946; MS024.001.141.00006 (Box 141)
  - 'Boursiers' (Scholarships), 1946; MS024.001.141.00007 (Box 141)
  - 'Boursiers' (Scholarships), 1946; MS024.001.141.00008 (Box 141)
  - Camp poem, 1925; MS024.001.141.00009 (Box 141)
    Poem about camp written by campers.
  - 'Carl and Elizabeth Heil', 1940 -- 1945; MS024.001.141.00010 (Box 141)
    Letters concerning the Heils internment in French camps during WWII and efforts by MacJannets and others to have them released.
  - C.I.A.M., 1948; MS024.001.141.00011 (Box 141)
    Letters concerning the Circle Internationale de la Musique.
  - 'Copies of all letters", 1950; MS024.001.141.00012 (Box 141)
    In folder marked 'copies of all letters.' From Jean MacJannet Foster.
  - 'Copies of all letters", 1950; MS024.001.141.00013 (Box 141)
  - 'Copies of all letters", 1950; MS024.001.141.00014 (Box 141)
  - Correspondence, 1936; MS024.001.141.00015 (Box 141)
    Letters mostly concerning MacJannet school in France.
  - Diary, 1921; MS024.001.141.00016 (Box 141)
    Donald MacJannet's diary while in Paris.
  - Early material, 1918; MS024.001.141.00017 (Box 141)
    Items Donald MacJannet kept from the 1910s. Includes a letter to MacJannet's Mother from his brother Malcolm who was imprisoned at Leavenworth during WWI.
  - Experiment in International Living, 1946; MS024.001.141.00018 (Box 141)
    Letters concerning Donald MacJannet's involvement with the Experiment in International Living and those from the group who went to the MacJannet camp in the summer of 1946.
  - Experiment in International Living, 1946; MS024.001.141.00019 (Box 141)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1946; MS024.001.141.00020 (Box 141)
  - Experiment in International Living, 1946; MS024.001.141.00021 (Box 141)
  - Family, 1937; MS024.001.141.00022 (Box 141)
    Material relating to MacJannet family genealogy. Also contains correspondence of Donald and Charlotte MacJannet and Jean MacJannet Foster
  - France - Dieleman, 1945; MS024.001.141.00023 (Box 141)
    Letters pertaining to Donald MacJannet's trip to France in 1945.
  - Germany and Luxembourg, 1950; MS024.001.141.00024 (Box 141)
    Letters pertaining to a trip Donald MacJannet organized through Germany and Luxembourg in 1950.
  - Gerda's course, 1963; MS024.001.141.00025 (Box 141)
    Material relating to Eutonia course taught by Gerda Alexander at the Priory in 1963.
  - Henri Prost, 1946 -- 1955; MS024.001.141.00026 (Box 141)
    Correspondence.
  - Hotels, Swiss trip, 1950; MS024.001.141.00027 (Box 141)
    Letters.
  - Inter-American Training, 1943; MS024.001.141.00028 (Box 141)
    Correspondence relating to Donald MacJannet's involvement/employment with the group.
  - Inter-American Training, 1943; MS024.001.141.00029 (Box 141)
  - Jean Foster, France, 1949; MS024.001.141.00030 (Box 141)
    Jean MacJannet Foster's correspondence with Donald and Charlotte MacJannet. Mostly relating to MacJannet camp.
  - Jochen Lathwesen, 1958; MS024.001.141.00031 (Box 141)
    Letters from Inge (Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's sister) and Hans Lathwesen and their son Jochen
  - Lawyer, 1959; MS024.001.141.00032 (Box 141)
    Correspondence and legal documents dealing with the Prieure/Priory.
  - Lawyer II, 1956 -- 1958; MS024.001.141.00033 (Box 141)
  - Letters, 1938; MS024.001.141.00034 (Box 141)
    MacJannet letters, dealing mostly with camp and campers, and travel arrangements.
  - Letters, 1950 -- 1980; MS024.001.141.00035 (Box 141)
    A collection of 'loose' letters to and from the MacJannets.
  - Letters, Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1969 -- 1970; MS024.001.141.00036 (Box 141)
    Letters relating to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet's interest in Rythmique, Eutonia and music.
  - Letters, Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, 1969 -- 1970; MS024.001.141.00037 (Box 141)
  - Letters, 1950; MS024.001.141.00038 (Box 141)
    Random assortment of camp related letters.
  - Loose letters, 1980; MS024.001.141.00039 (Box 141)
    Letters to the MacJannets.
  - Personal letters, 1946; MS024.001.141.00040 (Box 141)
    Some letters relating to Misplaced Persons, mostly personal letters.
  - Personal material, 1974; MS024.001.141.00041 (Box 141)
    Notes and lists for Donald MacJannet's birthday in 1974.
  - Plans for Priory, 1990; MS024.001.141.00042 (Box 141)
    Includes some architectural plans.
  - Prince Philip in Montreux, 1986; MS024.001.141.00043 (Box 141)
    Mostly correspondence including a letter from Prince Philip to Charlotte MacJannet.
  - Priory Entretiens, 1970; MS024.001.141.00044 (Box 141)
    Cards and responses to Entretiens (conversations/conferences).
  - Richard Powell, 1977 -- 1982; MS024.001.141.00045 (Box 141)
    Correspondence with Powell, a trustee of the MacJannet Foundation. Includes letters concerning the gift of the Priory to Tufts.
  - Richard Powell, 1977 -- 1982; MS024.001.141.00046 (Box 141)
  - Richard Powell, 1977 -- 1982; MS024.001.141.00047 (Box 141)
  - Speaking engagements, 1949; MS024.001.141.00048 (Box 141)
    Letters concerning Donald MacJannet's speaking engagements, mostly about France and WWII.
  - Speaking engagements, 1949; MS024.001.141.00049 (Box 141)
  - Speaking engagements, 1949; MS024.001.141.00050 (Box 141)
  - Speaking engagements, 1949; MS024.001.141.00051 (Box 141)
  - Toronto, 1973; MS024.001.141.00052 (Box 141)
    Letters from Canadian MacJannet relatives.
  - Travel, 1947; MS024.001.141.00053 (Box 141)
    Correspondence regarding travel arrangements.
  - Travel, 1947; MS024.001.141.00054 (Box 141)
  - Travel, 1947; MS024.001.141.00055 (Box 141)
  - Travel, 1947; MS024.001.141.00056 (Box 141)
  - Woodworth to 1978, MS024.001.141.00057 (Box 141)
    Correspondence with Anita and Lynn 'Woody' Woodworth. (Former teachers and counselors at MacJannet School and Camp.)
  - Camp, 1960 -- 1961; MS024.001.142.00001 (Box 142)
    Letters relating to the MacJannet camp, mostly between Jean Foster and Donald and Charlotte MacJannet.
  - Camp, 1960 -- 1961; MS024.001.142.00002 (Box 142)
  - Clan material, 1963; MS024.001.142.00003 (Box 142)
    Letters from MacJannet 'clan' members from around the world.
  - Donation letters, 1970 -- 1981; MS024.001.142.00004 (Box 142)
    Letters in reference to donations given by Donald MacJannet to non-profit/religious organizations. Actual receipts removed from the files.
  - Early material, 1905 -- 1916; MS024.001.142.00005 (Box 142)
    Material relating to Donald MacJannet's time at Medford High School and Tufts College. Includes some official school documents.
  - Early material, 1905 -- 1916; MS024.001.142.00006 (Box 142)
  - Early material, 1920; MS024.001.142.00007 (Box 142)
    Contains copy of The Albanian, magazine from St. Albanian School, mid-year 1920. Removed Tufts calendar from 1916 and Jumbo from 1916 (5/21/07) Original note:Material relating to Donald MacJannet's time at Medford High School and Tufts College. Includes some official school documents.
  - Early material, 1915; MS024.001.142.00008 (Box 142)
    Includes educational material from Medford high school and Tufts College. Also includes material from Bourget camp and the MacJannet Elms school.
  - Early material, 1915; MS024.001.142.00009 (Box 142)
  - Early material, 1915; MS024.001.142.00011 (Box 142)
  - Jean, 1956 -- 1958; MS024.001.142.00012 (Box 142)
    Correspondence of Jean MacJannet Foster, some relating to the MacJannet camp.
  - Jean, 1956 -- 1958; MS024.001.142.00013 (Box 142)
  - Jean, 1956 -- 1958; MS024.001.142.00014 (Box 142)
  - Letters, 1915 -- 1925; MS024.001.142.00015 (Box 142)
    Letters to Donald MacJannet. Those from the 1920s relate to MacJannet's time in Paris and the opening of the MacJannet school in St. Cloud, France.
  - Letters, 1920 -- 1970; MS024.001.142.00016 (Box 142)
    Letters sent to Herbert Jacobs, biographer of Donald MacJannet, with anecdotes and rememberances of life with MacJannet. Some have been edited by Donald MacJannet. Also includes letters from Donald MacJannet to Charlotte MacJannet during a 1965 trip to South Africa.
  - Letters, 1920 -- 1970; MS024.001.142.00017 (Box 142)
  - Letters, 1966; MS024.001.142.00018 (Box 142)
    Correspondence between Jean Foster and Donald and Charlotte MacJannet.
  - Personal letters, 1920 -- 1930; MS024.001.142.00019 (Box 142)
    Letters to Donald MacJannet in Paris. Includes some War Department letters.
  - Personal letters, 1941; MS024.001.142.00020 (Box 142)
    Letters written and received by the MacJannets while living in Sun Valley, Idaho.
  - Personal letters, 1941; MS024.001.142.00021 (Box 142)
  - Personal letters, 1947; MS024.001.142.00022 (Box 142)
    Letters, mostly to Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet, from her family in Germany. Includes letters from her father Otto Blensdorf, sister Ilse and her family, and her sister Inge and brother-in-law Hans Lathwesen. Also includes some Dalcroze (Rythmique) material.
  - Personal letters, 1947; MS024.001.142.00023 (Box 142)
  - Personal letters, 1947; MS024.001.142.00024 (Box 142)
  - Personal letters, 1947; MS024.001.142.00025 (Box 142)
  - Personal letters, 1947; MS024.001.142.00026 (Box 142)
  - Personal letters, 1947; MS024.001.142.00027 (Box 142)
  - Personal letters, 1947; MS024.001.142.00028 (Box 142)
  - Personal letters, 1960; MS024.001.142.00029 (Box 142)
    Loose letters to MacJannets, mostly from Jean MacJannet Foster.
  - Personal letters, 1960; MS024.001.142.00030 (Box 142)
  - Personal letters, Jean and Emory Foster, 1920 -- 1940; MS024.001.142.00031 (Box 142)
    Mostly letters to Jean MacJannet Foster but some to Emory Foster.
  - Priory, 1960; MS024.001.142.00032 (Box 142)
    Letters relating to the purchase and restoration of the Priory and the war indemnity money used to do so.
  - Publicity, 1930; MS024.001.142.00033 (Box 142)
    Newspaper clippings (have been photocopied) relating to the MacJannet camp and the Elms school. Letters as well.
  - Travel accounts of D. R. MacJannet, 1924; MS024.001.142.00034 (Box 142)
    Notes and material relating to travel made by Donald MacJannet. Includes commentary on WWI training and post-WWI Germany. Also inlcudes some material on camp Bourget.
  - Travel: Youth Argosy, 1949; MS024.001.142.00035 (Box 142)
    Material (letters mostly) relating to travel arrangements made by Donald MacJannet for campers and counselors through Youth Argosy. Includes military travel permits for MacJannet from 1948.
  - Travel: Youth Argosy, 1949; MS024.001.142.00036 (Box 142)
  - Travel: Youth Argosy, 1949; MS024.001.142.00037 (Box 142)
  - Camps, St. Cloud and personal, 1938 -- 1939; MS024.001.143.00001 (Box 143)
  - Camps, St. Cloud and personal, 1938 -- 1939; MS024.001.143.00002 (Box 143)
  - Correspondence, 1930; MS024.001.143.00003 (Box 143)
    Unsorted school and camp correspondence. Also includes some earlier letters about MacJannet's Scottish trip.
  - Correspondence, 1930; MS024.001.143.00004 (Box 143)
  - Correspondence, 1930; MS024.001.143.00005 (Box 143)
  - Counselors, 1980; MS024.001.143.00006 (Box 143)
    Letters from former camp counselors and campers.
  - Counselors, 1980; MS024.001.143.00007 (Box 143)
  - Counselors, 1980; MS024.001.143.00008 (Box 143)
  - Counselors, 1980; MS024.001.143.00009 (Box 143)
  - Dalcroze material, 1970; MS024.001.143.00010 (Box 143)
    Mostly correspondence. Includes notes from an Australian conference. Official documents, such as Latvian and American passports, belonging to Anna Antik were removed.
  - Dalcroze material, 1970; MS024.001.143.00011 (Box 143)
  - Dalcroze material, 1970; MS024.001.143.00012 (Box 143)
  - Employess, 1965 -- 1972; MS024.001.143.00013 (Box 143)
    Letters and applications to camp.
  - Employess, 1965 -- 1972; MS024.001.143.00014 (Box 143)
  - Family, 1971 -- 1973; MS024.001.143.00015 (Box 143)
    Correspondence with A. Imrie Dixon, a Medford High School teacher and principal, who was a cousin of D. MacJannet. Some of the letters contain commentary on the Vietnam Conflict and other isssues of the time.
  - Family, 1971 -- 1973; MS024.001.143.00016 (Box 143)
  - For America, 1946; MS024.001.143.00017 (Box 143)
    Includes some letters in Sweden.
  - French Officials, 1946; MS024.001.143.00018 (Box 143)
  - Kaye McKinnon, 1960; MS024.001.143.00019 (Box 143)
    Kaye McKinnon, a graduate of Jackson College, was a dancer and much involved in international arts. Folder includes letters and newspaper clippings, mostly of her ballet in Peru.
  - Letters, 1938 -- 1979; MS024.001.143.00020 (Box 143)
    Includes correspondence with staff and a packet from Tufts president Nils Wessel with commentary on his reunion by MacJannet.
  - Letters, 1962; MS024.001.143.00021 (Box 143)
  - Letters, 1970; MS024.001.143.00022 (Box 143)
  - Letters [B], 1966; MS024.001.143.00023 (Box 143)
    Letters contained within an alphabetical file folder.
  - Letters [C], 1966; MS024.001.143.00024 (Box 143)
  - Letters [D], 1966; MS024.001.143.00025 (Box 143)
  - Letters [E+F], 1966; MS024.001.143.00026 (Box 143)
  - Letters [G-J], 1966; MS024.001.143.00027 (Box 143)
  - Letters [K-O], 1966; MS024.001.143.00028 (Box 143)
  - Letters [P-R], 1966; MS024.001.143.00029 (Box 143)